[
  {
    "question": "Which is not part of system testing",
    "option1": "Regression Testing",
    "option2": "Sanity Testing",
    "option3": "Load Testing",
    "option4": "Unit Testing",
    "answerkey": 4
  },
  [
    {
      "question": "What is the main purpose of manual testing?",
      "option1": "To execute test cases using tools",
      "option2": "To find defects without automation",
      "option3": "To improve code performance",
      "option4": "To write test scripts",
      "answerkey": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which document describes how testing will be performed?",
      "option1": "Test Case",
      "option2": "Test Plan",
      "option3": "Bug Report",
      "option4": "Test Scenario",
      "answerkey": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of testing is done without using any automation tool?",
      "option1": "Performance Testing",
      "option2": "Automation Testing",
      "option3": "Manual Testing",
      "option4": "Load Testing",
      "answerkey": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Apache JMeter mainly used for?",
      "option1": "Manual testing",
      "option2": "Unit testing",
      "option3": "Performance and load testing",
      "option4": "Security testing",
      "answerkey": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which component is mandatory to create a JMeter test plan?",
      "option1": "Listener",
      "option2": "Thread Group",
      "option3": "Timer",
      "option4": "Assertion",
      "answerkey": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which testing ensures that new changes do not affect existing functionality?",
      "option1": "Smoke Testing",
      "option2": "Sanity Testing",
      "option3": "Regression Testing",
      "option4": "Load Testing",
      "answerkey": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which JMeter element is used to simulate multiple users?",
      "option1": "Sampler",
      "option2": "Thread Group",
      "option3": "Listener",
      "option4": "Controller",
      "answerkey": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which testing is performed to verify a small change in code?",
      "option1": "System Testing",
      "option2": "Regression Testing",
      "option3": "Sanity Testing",
      "option4": "Load Testing",
      "answerkey": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which document contains detailed steps to execute a test?",
      "option1": "Test Plan",
      "option2": "Test Case",
      "option3": "Test Summary Report",
      "option4": "Bug Life Cycle",
      "answerkey": 2
    }
  ]

]
